Daniel Felipe Polo Garcia

ABOUT ME

I am a web developer and mobile developer with all the benefits that React allows us to use, with 1 year and 1 month of experience in which I have had the opportunity to develop myself in the role of frontend participating in large projects and assisting my partners in their challenges.

EXPERIENCE

e-me Growth and Development Agency, Barranquilla(On-site) — Frontend developer

MAY 2022 - TODAY

- Support and improve advanced projects upon customer's request.
- Structuring, creating and optimizing new web projects.
- Layout and integration according to business logic.

Eureka DMS, Bogotá(Remote) - Junior frontend developer

DEC 2021 - MAY 2022

- Software and infrastructure technical support.
- Mobile software development.
- Layout and integration according to business logic.

FORMATION

Universidad del atlántico, Puerto colombia — Degree in mechanical engineering

JAN 2022 - TODAY, Puerto colombia

Universidad del atlántico, Barranquilla — Foreign language

course: English

JAN 2016 - JUL 2019, Puerto colombia

SKILLS

- React
- React Native (CLI)
- Nextjs
- Nodejs

- MongoDB
- HTML
- CSS
- Javascript / Typescript
- Ant design / Material UI / Bootstrap

ACHIEVEMENTS

In my career as a frontend developer I have been able to participate in major projects such as the creation of a mobile app for managing appointments for medical visits, medical product management and subscriptions, this app is called "Roota Two" which is essentially the support of medical visitors, in another opportunity I had the challenge of developing a functional clone of "algolia" by the hand of "meilisearch" that helps to be a powerful search engine and ultimately I am working on "casandra" a very complete ecommerce that has its own job portal and learning academy.

LANGUAGES

Spanish and English.